{
    "subject": "resource/Marisa_Pavan",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1932-06-19",
    "human_readable": "Marisa Pavan was born on June 19, 1932.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8972607851028442,
            "question": "When was Marisa Pavan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8110857605934143,
            "question": "In what decade was Marisa Pavan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7203131318092346,
            "question": "What nationality is Marisa Pavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7178448438644409,
            "question": "What month and day was Marisa Pavan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6419462561607361,
            "question": "Is Marisa Pavan's birthdate in the summer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6397609114646912,
            "question": "What is Marisa Pavan known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5361489057540894,
            "question": "In what year did Marisa Pavan come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5000859498977661,
            "question": "Is there any information about Marisa Pavan's parents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3844352960586548,
            "question": "Did Marisa Pavan have a successful acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2767506241798401,
            "question": "Has Marisa Pavan won any awards for her work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marisa Pavan was born on June 19, 1932.",
            "html": "dbpedia_669_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Marisa Pavan have a successful acting career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_669_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Marisa Pavan's parents?",
            "html": "dbpedia_669_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Marisa Pavan come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_669_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_669_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Marisa Pavan's birthdate as June 19, 1932."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in multiple documents. All of them confirm that Marisa Pavan was born on June 19, 1932."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}